hdtracks.com 2015-05-12

# Privacy Policy | HDtracks - The World's Greatest-Sounding Music Downloads

### HDTRACKS.COM TAKES YOUR PRIVACY SERIOUSLY.

Our website, www.HDtracks.com, and our HDtracks Store ("Digital Store") is the Internet’s Hi-Def Digital Download Store (TM). In order to make our Digital Store better for you we may collect information about you, your household (but not children under 18), and your use of your music collection. This Privacy Policy, which HDtracks has the right to amend from time to time, describes how and why we collect information from you, how we handle that information, and how and why we use that information. This Privacy Policy is part of our Terms of Service and applies to all information we collect or receive from you and your household.

### INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND WHY WE COLLECT IT

In order to provide you with convenient access to our service and information about your account and services relating to the HDtracks Digital Store, we collect the following information:

 **Registration**. In order to use our Digital Store and/or to sign up for our emailing list, you must provide us with certain personal information. Prior to purchasing downloads for the first time, you will be required to register and create an account with HDtracks ("HDtracks Account"). When you create your HDtracks Account, you will be required to provide a login name and password and your name, address and email address. You may also be asked to provide us with additional information, such as your age, gender, and other personal information about yourself or your family. We do NOT retain your credit card information. You may also be asked to provide us with additional information, such as your age, occupation, and internet service provider, but such information is not required.

Once you have registered with us, we may also collect other information about you, including your transactions with us, your service usage patterns, such as the pages on the HDtracks.com Website you have visited, searches you have conducted on our site and the amount of time you have spent on our Website. If you contact us, we may keep a record of your correspondence. If you have registered with us, we may collect information about what music files you possess on the PC you use to sign up with our service and any other PC's networked to that PC. We may also collect information regarding where you obtained that music. We may collect information concerning the bit rate of the encode of music files contained on your PC and/or any PC connected to that PC

* * *

**Promotions.** As part of the process to create a HDtracks Account or to participate in certain promotions offered by HDtracks such as entering sweepstakes, contests, surveys, newsletters, etc., in addition to name, address, and email address, you may be asked to provide certain information which, by itself, does not personally identify you. For example, you may be asked to provide information concerning your music or other entertainment preferences, purchasing habits, and the like. HDtracks may request this information in order to enhance your experience by understanding you better and to also make you aware of new services, programs or offers in which you may be interested.

* * *

**Visiting the Site.** We keep track of the domains from which people visit our Website, www.HDtracks.com. We may track the country or zip code of visitors to our Website and of those downloading or attempting to download products from our Digital Store. We analyze this data for trends and statistics, and for federal export law compliance when required. This information is analyzed at an aggregate level and is not considered personally identifiable. We may also collect statistical data on all users of our Website, including: the Internet Protocol (IP) address of the user's computer, the referring URL, if any, and the browser software identification. Certain referring URLs and IP addresses may contain or suggest personally identifiable information.

* * *

**Forums and Chat Rooms.** If you choose to post messages to our message boards, forums, or chat rooms or other message areas or leave feedback for other users, we may collect or track that information. We retain this information as necessary to resolve disputes, provide customer support and troubleshoot problems, and as otherwise permitted by law. If you send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, or if other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities or postings on the Site, we may collect such information into a file specific to you.

* * *

**Mailing Lists.** In order to keep you informed about our services, we may send e-mails and announcements that are needed for the administration of our Website and service. We also give our users the option of joining our mailing list to receive additional information about our Website, services and offers.

* * *

**Use of Cookies.** We may use data collection devices such as "cookies" (small text files that are placed on your computer's hard drive for record-keeping purposes) to assist us in providing our services. Cookies make using the Site easier by, among other things, saving your passwords and preferences for you, helping identify you whenever you return to our Site, and reducing the number of times you are required to enter your password during a session. Cookies can also help us provide information that is targeted toward your interests and preferences. Most Internet browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. However, you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to alert you when a cookie is being sent (note: you may need to consult your browser's "Help" area for instructions on how to do that). If you choose to disable your cookies setting or refuse to accept a cookie, you may not be able to use certain features on the Site and you may be required to reenter your password more frequently during a session. Please note, that if you set your browser to block acceptance of cookies, this may affect your ability to use the HDtracks service or enter our Website.

### YOUR INFORMATION AND HOW WE USE IT

In general, HDtracks may use non-personally identifiable information about you to improve and enhance the services we provide. HDtracks may share this information with the suppliers of content on the service, affiliates and other entities in non-personal form to show general demographic and preference information among users of the HDtracks service or for other purposes. This information may include usage and demographic data, but it will not include personal information (such as your email address). If you provide HDtracks with personally identifiable information, we will take reasonable and appropriate steps to protect this information. Except as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy, or our Terms of Service, HDtracks will not disclose, share, sell or rent personally identifiable information collected on our Website to any third party without your prior consent. We do not share your credit card account information with any third parties, other than order processing and credit card clearance service providers as described below.

 **Third Parties in General.** We work with third parties who provide services, which may include website hosting, order processing, credit card clearance, data analysis, customer service, promotion fulfillment, and other services of an administrative nature. Personal information, including financial information, may be shared with such third parties for the purpose of providing such services to you. We seek to impose confidentiality obligations on such service providers. Also, entities into which our company is merged, or to which our assets, site or operations have been transferred or sold, will be able to use your personal information under the terms of this Privacy Policy. We also reserve the right to disclose personal information to third parties when we believe in good faith that the law requires it, to enforce our Terms of Service, to protect the rights, property, safety, or security of HDtracks, its content providers, or the public, to respond to an emergency, or as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy.

### OUR SECURITY

We use reasonable security methods to protect the data that resides on our servers. However, because no security system is impenetrable, we cannot guarantee the security of our servers. It is also possible that information you supply to us will be intercepted during transmission.

Whenever you give HDtracks sensitive information (e.g., credit card numbers), HDtracks will take commercially reasonable steps to protect such information by establishing a secure connection with your Web browser. HDtracks employs an industry standard technology known as a secure-socket-layer ("SSL") to protect the transmission of payment information from the HDtracks Network to our servers. We do not share your credit card information with any parties not directly involved in processing or completing your purchase.

To help protect your HDtracks Account information, please keep your password secure. We suggest that you pick a non-obvious password that mixes numbers and letters. In addition, we recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. Ultimately, you are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and any HDtracks Account information.

Remember to sign out of your HDtracks Account, and close your browser window whenever you leave your computer. This is to ensure that others cannot access your personal information, because your computer may be accessible to others or used in a shared setting. HDtracks's Privacy Policy does not extend to anything that is inherent in the operation of the Internet, and therefore beyond HDtracks's control, and is not to be applied in any manner contrary to applicable law or governmental regulation.

* * *

### LINKS

HDtracks may allow certain invited entities to be included in a list of links found on the HDtracks.com site. However, any link to a page which displays a URL other than a domain name that contains HDtracks.com in the address window of your browser is a link to a site outside of our service and therefore outside the control of HDtracks. These other sites may send their own cookies to you, collect data or solicit personal information. HDtracks cannot guarantee and is not responsible for the content of outside sites. While HDtracks strives to protect our visitors' personal information and privacy, we cannot guarantee the security and privacy of any information you disclose at other sites, and you do so at your own risk.

###   
REGARDING PERSONS UNDER 18 YEARS OF AGE

The Website and the services provided thereon are intended for access and use strictly by adults 18 years and older. As such, it is not HDtracks's intention to collect nor maintain any personally identifiable information from persons under 18 years of age. Although HDtracks does not seek to collect any information from persons under the age of 18, should you find that your child has submitted his/her information, HDtracks will make reasonable efforts to delete a child's information from its database upon request. You may request to have such information purged from HDtracks's database by sending an email request to privacy@HDtracks.com. In the event that you are requesting such information to be purged from HDtracks's database, please make sure to include the correct email address that was submitted by the child.

### HOW TO REVIEW, UPDATE OR DELETE YOUR REGISTRATION INFORMATION

As part of your use of our services, you are responsible for updating your submitted registration information so that it is current, accurate, and complete. In order to update your registration information, please access your HDtracks Account and make the desired change. You may also access your HDtracks Account in order to change your user preferences.

Please note that by using our Website and/or our software and the services provided therein, you signify your agreement to this Privacy Policy, as it may be amended from time to time. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use our Website, software, or the services provided therein. We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy. We will provide notice to you of any material changes by any reasonable means including sending an email to the most recently updated address in your HDtracks Account and/or posting such notice and the amended policy on the HDtracks Website and in the links contained in our software. Your continued use of our Website and/or software following changes to this Privacy Policy will mean that you accept and agree to the changes and that any information collected or provided after such change will be governed by the updated Privacy Policy.

HDtracks.com may contain links to other websites and there may be instances where other websites may be co-branded and/or otherwise affiliated with the HDtracks name. These sites may have privacy policies which differ from that of HDtracks.

HDtracks is dedicated to protecting your personal information and welcomes comments and questions on this Privacy Policy. If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, please send an email to [info@HDtracks.com](mailto:info@HDtracks.com). If you would like to contact HDtracks for any other reason, please write to HDtracks, Inc., PO Box 1368 Radio City Station, NY NY 10101, Attn: Customer Service.
